Sheetal Bohara (Jain)

Current Address: Tata Amantra Society; L-092 Apurva Building, Kalyan Junction, Bhiwandi,

Mumbai-Nashik Express way; Mumbai (421302), Maharashtra, India

Permanent Address 126, Anjani Nagar, Airport Road; Indore (452005), Madhya Pradesh, India

Mobile Number: 9755018181

E-Mail: sheetalpamecha1403@gmail.com

To,

The HR Department

I am submitting herewith my resume for your perusal and favourable consideration for the suitable post in your organization.

I am 'Master of Business Administration' (MBA-Finance & Marketing) with 02 years of experience as Revenue cycle representative..

I am a self-motivated and energetic individual, with superb interpersonal skills who is driven by a strong desire to achieve results and improve the standards of quality. I work effectively as part of a team and have a good level of emotional intelligence along with superb strategic thinking and organizational skills.

On a personal level I am humble enough to escalate issues and seek assistance when I need to. I possess superb communication skills and can quickly establish rapport and credibility with staff at all levels.

I am confident that I can perform assign responsibilities while maintaining professionalism and a teamwork mindset in the workplace.

If you find me to be a suitable person for your position then do not hesitate to contact me by phone, letter or email.

Finally, thank you very much for taking the time to read my application along with my enclosed resume.

Thanking you in anticipation

Yours sincerely,

Sheetal Bohara

SHEETAL BOHARA

Email

sheetalpamecha1403@gmail.com

Current Address:

Tata Amantra Society;

Apurva Building, Flat No. L-092

Kalyan Junction, Mumbai

(421302), Maharashtra, India

Permanent Address:

126, Anjani Nagar,

Airport Road

Indore (M.P.), 452005

Mobile No.

9755018181

Personal Data

Date of Birth : 14/10/1987

Sex : Female
Nationality : Indian
Caste : Jain

Marital Status : Married

Languages Known: Hindi,

English

Hobbies: Cooking,

Listening to music

Assets:

- Effective Communication skill and leadership qualities.
- 2. Highly motivated to work as a team.
- Quick implementation of instructions.

Objective

Intend to build a career with leading organization where I can groom myself and at the same time prove an asset to the organization. Willing to work as a key player in challenging and creative environment.

Professional Experience

 Company: Inventurus Knowledge Solution Healthcare Pvt. Ltd. (IKS Healthcare Pvt. Ltd.)
 (Airoli, Mumbai, Maharashtra)

Duration: Since 24th November 2021 to Till Date Designation: Revenue Cycle Representative

Job Responsibilities

- Payment Posting for mediclaim documents for user as well client.
- Handling of many documents related to mediclaim such as
 - Audit & Audit Response
 - Re-determination
 - Reconsideration
 - Refunds
 - Correspondence Posting
 - Patients Address Rectification

Academic Experience

School: Geeta Devi Agarwal Public School (Sanawad, Madhya Pradesh)

Duration: Since 6th December 2013 to 15th April 2015 Designation: Office Administration Executive

Job Responsibilities

- Collection and Maintenance of Data.
- Assist in coordination of events, meetings and curricular activities.
- Managing and maintaining the operation of general office.
- Handle scheduling, record-keeping and reporting.

Academic Credentials

Qualification	Institution	Board/University	Year	%
Master of Business Administration (Finance & Marketing)	Sushila Devi Bansal College	DAVV University, Indore	2009-2011	64 %
Bachelor of Science	Holkar Science College, Indore	DAVV University, Indore	2005-2008	61%
H.S.C	St. Mary's Higher Secondary School, Barwaha	Madhya Pradesh State board	2005	79 %
S.S.C	St. Mary's Higher Secondary School, Barwaha	Madhya Pradesh State board	2003	58 %

Project Undertaken

 MBA Major Research Project on "The distribution system of HUL in rural areas of Indore City.".

Achievements

- Completed 5 years of B.A. in Kathak
- Winner in inter college Ad MAD competition
- Actively participated in IBL (Indore B-School League) conducted by IIM, Indore.

Computer Literacy

- · Operating System: Windows, XP
- Working Knowledge of following Software's:
 Microsoft Office package (MS word, Excel, Power point)

Industrial Training and Industrial Tour

• Industrial training in Motilal Oswal Pvt. Ltd., Indore for 45 days regarding equity market, product training, business development activities.

Declaration

I hereby declare that all the details furnished above are true to the best of my knowledge.

(Sheetal Bohara)